A Finding Aid to the Holly Solomon Gallery Records, circa 1948-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.hollsolg
Archives of American Art
- Inventory Records, 1975-2001; Series 5; (Boxes 48-66, 157-162; 25.0 linear feet)
  - Card File: Mitchell, Joan, 1987-1991 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Miralda, 1990-1991 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Mogavero, Michael, 1980-1984; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Card File: M Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Nahas, Nabil, 1986-1988 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Natz, Helga, 1997-2000 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Nonas, Richard, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Card File: N Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Oldenburg, Claus, 1981-1984 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Oppenheim, Dennis, 1985-1991 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Ostendarp, Carl, 1989-1991 (Box 60)
  - Card File: O'Carrol, John, 1986 (Box 60)
  - Card File: O Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 60)
  - Card File: Paik, Nam June, 1986-2000; (13 folders) (Box 61)
  - Card File: Patkin, Izhar, 1998-1999 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Perlman, Cara, 1994 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Perrone, Jeff, 1997 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Perna, Luciano, 1989-1990 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Pfaff, Judy, 1981-1999 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Phillips, Richard, 1987-1988 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Picasso, Pablo, 1984 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Polke, Sigmar, 1982-1996 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Pollock, Jackson, 1996-1999; (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Card File: Price, Ken, 1984-1985 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Provisor, Janis, 1978-1987; (3 folders) (Box 62)
  - Card File: P Miscellanous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Rady, Elsa, 1986-2000; (4 folders) (Box 62)
  - Card File: Rappleye, Jon, 1998-1999 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Ripps, Rodney, 1979-1982 (Box 62)
  - Card File: Rupp, Christy, 1994-1996 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Rush, Cecily, 1995-1997 (Box 63)
  - Card File: R Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Scharf, Kenny, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Schneeman, George, 1975-1982; (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Card File: Shostak, Ed, 1975-1980 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Schnydes, Jean-Frederic, undated (Box 63)
  - Card File: Smith, Alexis, 1975-1985 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Smyth, Ned, 1975-1990; (3 folders) (Box 63)
  - Card File: Spoldi, Aldo, 1980-1983 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Stikas, Marianne, 1978-1982 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Stimm, Thomas, 1985-1986 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Swarts, Charles, 1994-1995 (Box 63)
  - Card File: S Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 63)
  - Card File: Tuttle, Richard, 1988-1990 (Box 63)
  - Card File: T Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 63)
  - Card File: V Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Waplington, Nick, 1997-1999 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Warhol, Andy, 1987-1999 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Weegee, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Wegman, William, 1981-1991 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Wegman, William, 1981-1991 (Box 159)
  - Card File: Wegman, William, 1981-1991 (Box 160)
  - Card File: Wegman, William, 1981-1991 (Box 161)
  - Card File: Wegman, William, 1981-1991 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Weiner, Lawrence, 1990-1994 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Weiner, Lawrence, 1990-1994 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Wells, Lynton, 1975-2001 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Wesselmann, Tom, 1975-2001 (Box 162)
  - Card File: West, David, 1975-2001 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Wiener, Daniel, 1975-2001 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Williams, Neil, 1975-2001 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Wilson, Donald Roller, 1984-1998 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Wilson, Donald Roller, 1984-1998 (Box 162)
  - Card File: Wynne, Rob, 1994-2000; (3 folders) (Box 64)
  - Card File: Wynne, Rob, 1994-2000 (Box 162)
  - Card File: W Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Y Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 64)
  - Card File: Zucker, Joe, 1977-1997; (2 folders) (Box 64)
  - Card File: Z Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 64)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Inventory, undated; (4 folders) (Box 64)
  - Holly Solomon Personal Inventory Pre 1975, circa 1980s (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Personal Collection Proposed Values, circa 1980s (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Inventory Lists, 1975-1987, 1992 (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Inventory, September 1987 (Box 65)
  - Inventory List, 1994 (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Available Inventory, 1998 (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Available Inventory, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Inventory, 2001 (Box 65)
  - Distribution and Missing Works Lists, circa 1990-1992 (Box 65)
  - Checklists, 1997-1999 (Box 65)
  - Old Check Lists, circa 1990s; (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous Inventory Sheets and Lists, undated (Box 65)
  - Stocklist, Holly Solomon Editions, circa 1980s (Box 65)
  - Holly Solomon Editions, H-Z, 1980-1985; (12 folders) (Box 65)
  - Evelyn Lauder Photo Inventory Sheets, 1990-1994 (Box 66)
  - Nam June Paik Inventory Sheets, undated (Box 66)
  - Izhar Patkin Prints Inventory Sheets, 1994-1995 (Box 66)
  - Master Inventory of Gallery Artists, Africano-Wegman, circa 1975-1990s; (5 folders) (Box 66)
  - Miscellaneous Artist Inventory, A-M, circa 1975-1990s; (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Miscellaneous Artist Inventory, N-Z, circa 1975-1990s; (3 folders) (Box 66)
- Administrative Records, circa 1980-2003; Series 6; (Boxes 67-81, OV 202; 15.1 linear feet)
  Administrative records contain general office materials such as phone messages books, notebooks used by staff, exhibition guest books, and business diaries. Records primarily cover the 1980s and 1990s. Business diaries are in day calendar format and contain appointment, contact, and event information. Tucked and stapled into the books are business cards, invitations, announcements, and occasionally correspondence. Each diary is one calendar year and some years have more than one diary while other years are missing. Also found are diaries used only for Holly Solomon Editions; a Holly Solomon Editions stamp on the inside cover page designates the diary's use.
  The "Dear Diary" files parallel the business diaries but are not specifically calendar oriented. These diaries were compiled in binders by Holly Solomon, arranged by month and year, and contain a collection of contact information and notes on clients and events. Some of the diaries were maintained for a specific event, such as the Armory Art Fair of 1999. Researchers should note that additional "Dear Diary" materials may be contained within specific event folders found in Series 3: Subject Files. Diary material has been removed from binders into archival folders, but the original order has been maintained.
  Exhibition binders found in this series contain layout and artist information for exhibitions in the early 1980s. Also found are boxes of unsorted mail and other documents that were never filed, mail from artists seeking representation, artists' biographies, and a file of Holly's notes.
  - Rolodex, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 67)
  - General Office Notebooks, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 67)
  - Rolodex, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 68)
  - General Office Notebooks, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 68)
  - Address Book, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 68)
  - Phone Message Books, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 68)
  - Phone Message Books, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 69)
  - Phone Message Books, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 70)
  - Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 70)
  - Exhibition Binders, 1980-1985; (2 binders) (Box 70)
  - Corporate Records Book: HDS Inc, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Corporate Records Book: Holly Solomon Gallery Inc, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Phone Message Books, circa 1980s (Box 71)
  - Guest Books, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 72)
  - Business Diaries, 1981-1984 (Box 73)
  - Business Diaries, 1984-1987 (Box 74)
  - Business Diaries, 1988-1991 (Box 75)
  - Business Diaries, 1992-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 76)
  - "Dear Diary,", September 1987-March 1988; (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", February-December 1990; (4 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", 1991; (4 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", January-June 1992; (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", 1996 (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", 1997 (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary," Museums, 1997-1998; (4 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", 1998 (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", January-May 1999; (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - "Dear Diary,", June-December 1999; (2 folders) (Box 78)
  - "Dear Diary,", 2000; (4 folders) (Box 78)
  - "Dear Diary,", January-October 2001; (3 folders) (Box 78)
  - "Dear Diary,", 2002; (2 folders) (Box 78)
  - "Dear Diary,", January-April 2003 (Box 78)
  - Armory Art Fair "Dear Diary,", 1999 (Box 78)
  - ADAA "Dear Diary,", 1999 (Box 78)
  - Business Diaries, 1999, 2001 (Box 78)
  - Mailing List, 1999 (Box 78)
  - Artist Bios, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 79)
  - Mail from Prospective Artists, circa 1990s (Box 79)
  - Travel - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 80)
  - Correspondence to Holly Solomon Gallery from Holly, 1991-1994 (Box 80)
  - Holly's Notes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 80)
  - Unsorted Office Files and Correspondence, circa 1990s (Box 80)
  - Unsorted Office Files and Correspondence, circa 1990s (Box 81)
  - Architectural Plans, Holly Solomon Gallery, 1993 (Box OV 202)
- Sales and Loan Records, circa 1975-2001; Series 7; (Boxes 82-87; 6.0 linear feet)
  The sales and loan records consist of in and out sheets, consignments, and sales invoices. In and out sheets tracked works as they moved in and out of the gallery and are limited to the date span of 1994-2000. For similar information please see the card files in Series 5: Inventory Records. Invoice records are divided between works that were on consignment and those works which were not; invoices date from 1978-2001 while the consignment invoices date from 1978-2000. Also in this series are sales and loan logs and files that track the same information but from different search points, including sales by artist. Files regarding Holly Solomon Editions invoicing are labeled as such.
  Invoices are arranged by invoice number in ascending numerical order, which also follows a chronological order. The invoices have three numbering sequences due to changes in invoicing practices in the gallery. Material has been removed from binders into archival folders, but the original order has been maintained.
  - In Sheets, 1994-2000; (15 folders) (Box 82)
  - In Sheets, "City Folk" Exhibit, 1995-1996; (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Out Sheets, 1994-1999; (9 folders) (Box 83)
  - Consignment Invoices Nos. 301-775, 1978-1986; (5 folders) (Box 83)
  - Consignment Invoices Nos. 776-987, 1986-1989; (3 folders) (Box 84)
  - Consignment Invoices Nos. 89-00094 - 93-00035, 1989-1993; (10 folders) (Box 84)
  - Consignment Invoices Nos. 1040-1355, 1993-2000; (5 folders) (Box 84)
  - Consignment by Artist, circa 1980s (Box 84)
  - Consignment by Artist, circa 1980s (Box 85)
  - Consignment by Artist, Holly Solomon Editions, circa 1980s (Box 85)
  - Consignment Invoices Nos. 767-1017, Holly Solomon Editions, 1986-1988; (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - Consignment, circa 1975-1980 (Box 85)
  - Cincinnati Art Musuem Consignment, circa 1975-1980 (Box 85)
  - Liatowitsch Consignment, circa 1975-1980 (Box 85)
  - Segal Consignment, circa 1975-1980 (Box 85)
  - Consignment Isreal - J. Kiriaty, circa 1975-1980 (Box 85)
  - Sales Journal, 1993-1995 (Box 85)
  - Sales by Artist, circa 1970s (Box 85)
  - Loans, circa 1986-1989 (Box 85)
  - Invoices Nos. 367-2000, 1978-1981; (10 folders) (Box 85)
  - Invoices Nos. 2001-4400, 1981-1987; (16 folders) (Box 86)
  - Invoices Nos. 4401-4739, 1987-1989; (3 folders) (Box 87)
  - Invoices Nos. 89-00015 - 93-000109, 1989-1993; (8 folders) (Box 87)
  - Invoices Nos. 0009-0611, 1993-1999; (5 folders) (Box 87)
  - Invoices, 2001; (2 folders) (Box 87)
- Financial and Legal Records, circa 1969-2001; Series 8; (Boxes 88-114, 191, 192; 27.7 linear feet)
  This series contains financial files maintained by the gallery, including shipping and trucking invoices and records, tax and insurance information, and accounting statements and reports. Also found in this series are unpaid and paid bills, check stubs, petty cash receipts, and several ledgers. One box of legal records documents issues with the landlord of the gallery space.
  The financial files have been grouped together at the box level but are currently unprocessed.
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 88)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 89)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 90)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 91)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 92)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 93)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 94)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 95)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 96)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 97)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 98)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 99)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 100)
  - Loose Ledger Pages, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 100)
  - Petty Cash, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 100)
  - Petty Cash and Receipts, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 101)
  - Receipts, circa 1990s (Box 102)
  - Bills Unpaid, circa 1990s (Box 102)
  - Check Stubs, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 103)
  - Bills Paid, 2000-2001 (Box 103)
  - Paid Bills, A-Fe, circa 1990s (Box 104)
  - Paid Bills, Fi-Pa, circa 1990s (Box 105)
  - Paid Bills, Q-Z, circa 1990s (Box 106)
  - Paid Bills, A-F, circa 1990-1992 (Box 107)
  - Paid Bills, F- New York Telephone, circa 1990-1992 (Box 108)
  - Paid Bills, General, circa 1995-1996 (Box 109)
  - Financial Files, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 110)
  - Check Stubs, 1969-1976, 1987 (Box 110)
  - Ledger, 1976-1987 (Box 111)
  - Ledger, 1980-1986 (Box 111)
  - Ledger, Cash Receipts, 1993-1995 (Box 112)
  - Ledger, Bank Records, 1978-1988 (Box 112)
  - Ledger, Cash Disbursements, 1993-1995 (Box 112)
  - Gallery Systems Accounting Binder, undated (Box 112)
  - General Ledger, 1993-1994 (Box 112)
  - General Journal, 1993-1995 (Box 112)
  - Ledger, 1985-1986 (Box 112)
  - Ledger, 1987 (Box 112)
  - Ledger, A/R, A/P, Procedures, 1993,1994 (Box 112)
  - Ledgers, circa 1980s (Box 113)
  - Legal Papers, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 114)
  - Ledger, circa 1980s (Box 191)
  - Ledger, circa 1991-1992 (Box 192)
- Printed Material, circa 1968-2002; Series 9; (Boxes 115-135, 193-194, OV 203-222, RD 223; 23.5 linear feet)
  This series consists of artist clippings, gallery exhibition catalogs, press releases, posters, and miscellaneous books, magazines, and clippings regarding the gallery. The artist clipping files contain exhibition announcements, newspaper clippings, magazine articles, and invitations to events. The quantity of material in these files varies greatly by artist. Artists such as Nicholas Africano, Laurie Anderson, Robert Kuchner, Gordon Matta-Clark, Judy Pfaff, and William Wegman have large quantities of material. Also found are clippings pertaining to the Pattern and Design art movement, exhibition catalogs and announcements, and a box of books Holly Solomon kept in her office.
  Most of the posters in this series are for exhibitions for artists represented by Holly Solomon Gallery; however, posters for exhibitions put on by other galleries are included. Also found are posters artist Eric Drooker illustrated for local NYC causes and organizations.
  - Clippings: Africano, Nicholas, 1974-1995 (Box 115)
  - Clippings: Anderson, Laurie, 1974-1995 (Box 115)
  - Clippings: Anderson, Laurie, 1974-1995 (Box 116)
  - Clippings: Bark, Jared, 1974-1983 (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Barry, Robert, 1991-1995 (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Carlson, Mary, circa 1990s (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Chamberlain, John, 1998 (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Christo, 1995 (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Davis, Brad, 1974-1995 (Box 117)
  - Clippings: Davis, Brad, 1974-1995 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Drooker, Eric, 1996 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Eigenheer, Marianne, 1983-1992 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Etkin, Susan, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Garrin, Paul, 1995-1996 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Jimenez, Elisa, circa 1990s (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Kirili, Alain, 1987-1992 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Kempinger, Herwig, 1991-1992 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Kushner, Robert, 1977-1992 (Box 118)
  - Clippings: Kushner, Robert, 1977-1992 (Box 119)
  - Clippings: Kushner, Robert, 1977-1992 (Box 120)
  - Clippings: Lowe, Jean, circa 1990s (Box 120)
  - Clippings: MacConnel, Kim, 1974-1995 (Box 120)
  - Clippings: MacConnel, Kim, 1974-1995 (Box 121)
  - Clippings: Majore, Frank, 1989-1994 (Box 121)
  - Clippings: Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1971-1995 (Box 121)
  - Clippings: Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1971-1995 (Box 122)
  - Clippings: Miller, Melissa, 1983-1995 (Box 122)
  - Clippings: Miller, Melissa, 1983-1995 (Box 123)
  - Clippings: Meyer, Melissa, 1990-1995 (Box 123)
  - Clippings: Oppenheim, Dennis, circa 1980s (Box 123)
  - Clippings: Paik, Nam June, 1983-1995 (Box 123)
  - Clippings: Paik, Nam June, 1983-1995 (Box 124)
  - Clippings: Patkin, Izhar, 1982-1995 (Box 124)
  - Clippings: Perlman, Cara, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 125)
  - Clippings: Perrone, Jeff, circa 1990s (Box 125)
  - Clippings: Pfaff, Judy, 1980-1991 (Box 125)
  - Clippings: Pollack, Barbara, 1997 (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Rady, Elsa, 1987-1995 (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Ripps, Rodney, circa 1980s (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Rokeby, David, 1996-1998 (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Rupp, Christy, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Schmidt, Thomas Lanigan, 1980-1995 (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Smyth, Ned, 1975-1995 (Box 126)
  - Clippings: Smyth, Ned, 1975-1995 (Box 127)
  - Clippings: Solomon, Thomas, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 127)
  - Clippings: Solomon, John, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 127)
  - Clippings: Solomon Foundation, 1987 (Box 127)
  - Clippings: Solomon - Living with Art, circa 1989 (Box 128)
  - Clippings: Holly Solomon File, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Clippings: Wegman, William, 1974-1995 (Box 128)
  - Clippings: Wegman, William, 1974-1995 (Box 129)
  - Clippings: Wegman, William, 1974-1995 (Box 130)
  - Clippings: Wynne, Rob, 1996-1997 (Box 130)
  - Clippings: Miscellaneous Clippings, circa 1975-2002 (Box 130)
  - Clippings: "P and D" [Pattern and Decoration], circa 1970s-1980s (Box 131)
  - Holly Solomon Gallery Catalogs and Publications, circa 1975-2002 (Box 132)
  - Books from Holly Soloman's Office, circa 1975-2002 (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Catalogs and Publications, circa 1975-2002 (Box 134)
  - Press Release Binder, 1994-1999 (Box 134)
  - Nam June Paik Press Binder, 1982-2000 (Box 135)
  - Invitations, 1997 (Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1975-2002 (Box 135)
  - Dag Alveng's Book, Asylum, 1986 (Box 193)
  - Eric Drooker Posters, undated (Box 194)
  - David Bradshaw Poster, 1991 (Box 194)
  - Dag Alveng Poster, undated (Box 194)
  - Poster, undated (Box 194)
  - Posters, ArtAttack Exhibition; Art Against Aids; Arch Connelly, 1979, 1987, undated (Box OV 203)
  - Posters, Barry, Robert; Boshier, Eric, 1989, 1990, 1994 (Box OV 204)
  - Posters, Chryssa; The Lilja Collection; Matta-Clark, Gordon; Patkin, Izhar, 1968, 1977, 1987, undated (Box OV 205)
  - Posters, Drooker, Eric, undated (Box OV 206)
  - Posters, Drooker, Eric, 1993-1995 (Box OV 207)
  - Posters, Gray, Spaulding/Yourgrau, Barry; Roller-Wilson, Donald, circa 1980s, 1983 (Box OV 208)
  - Posters, Kushner/Friedman [Robert Kushner/Ed Friedman], 1979; (6 OV folders) (Box OV 209-214)
  - Posters, Kushner, Robert; MacConnel, Kim; Miralda; Pfaff, Judy, 1987, 1988, 1995, undated (Box OV 215)
  - Posters, MacConnel, Kim; Coach, 1982, 1999 (Box OV 216)
  - Posters, Paik, Nam June, 1986, 1990, 1996, undated (Box OV 217)
  - Poster, Paik, Nam June, 2000 (Box RD 223)
  - Posters, Rogers, Wendy, 1980; (2 OV folders) (Box OV 218-219)
  - Posters, Wegman, William, 1982-1993, undated (Box OV 220)
  - Posters, Smith, Alexis; Zucker, Joe, 1981-1982 (Box OV 221)
  - Framed Print on Fabric, MacConnel, Kim, 1988 (Box OV 222)
- Photographic Material, circa 1969-2000; Series 10; (Boxes 136-156, 194-196, 201, OV 224; 22.2 linear feet)
  Photographic material includes photographs and slides documenting artists' work and gallery exhibitions. Found here are black and white and color photographs, including many polaroids, arranged by artist or by subject. Photographs primarily depict artwork, artwork installed for a gallery exhibition, or gallery performances. This series contains very few photographs of artists. The amount of material found within these files is varied and researchers should note that some photographic material can also be found in files in Series 4: Artists' Files. While most slides are housed separately, photograph files may also include scattered slides, as well as negatives and transparencies. The majority of files are by artist, but there are also files of photographs by subject. Subjects include various exhibitions, gallery flood damage, and events. Of note are photographs from the opening of the gallery's first exhibition in 1975.
  The series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  10.1: Photographs, circa 1969-2000
  10.2: Slides, circa 1975-2000
  Photographs by artist and slides by artist are in alphabetical order by artists' last name. Among the photographs arranged by artist items may be arranged by year, exhibition, performance, or format, while other files have no particular arrangement. The slides series is arranged in three ways: in folders arranged alphabetically by artist, in binders alphabetically by artist, and in slide boxes by artist. The first set was marked as a duplicate set and most likely mimics what is in the alphabetical binders.
  - Photographs, circa 1969-2000; 10.1
    - Acconci, Vito, circa 1975-2000 (Box 136)
    - Africano, Nicholas, circa 1975-2000; (9 folders) (Box 136)
    - Anderson, Laurie, circa 1975-2000 (Box 136)
    - Artschwager, Richard, circa 1975-2000 (Box 136)
    - Anzinger, circa 1975-2000 (Box 136)
    - Bark, Jared, 1972-circa 2000; (3 folders) (Box 137)
    - Barry, Robert, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Basquiat, Jean-Michel, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Baxter, Glen, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Blishe [Buthe, Michel], circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Boetti, Alighiero, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Bowman, John, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Boyle, Kevin, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Brathwaite, Fred, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Brugger, Susanne, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Burnley, Gary, circa 1975-2000; (2 folders) (Box 137)
    - Cady, Sam, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Carlson, Mary, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Chagall, Marc, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Chamberlain, J., circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Chase, Lousia, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Chryssa, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Combas, Robert, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Connelly, Arch, circa 1975-2000 (Box 137)
    - Davis, Brad, 1971-1980; (2 folders) (Box 137)
    - Davis, Brad, 1981-1989; (2 folders) (Box 138)
    - Davis/Smyth [Brad Davis/Ned Smyth], 1977, 1981; (2 folders) (Box 138)
    - de Kooning, Willem, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Dennis, Donna, 1973-circa 2000; (3 folders) (Box 138)
    - Dufy, Raoul, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Etkin, Suzan, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Eigenheer, Marianne, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Fontana, Lucio, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Garabedian, Charles, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Garrin, Paul, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, circa 1975-2000 (Box 138)
    - Girouard, Tina, circa 1975-2000; (2 folders) (Box 138)
    - Girouard, Tina, 1973-1983; (3 folders) (Box 139)
    - Goldberg, Maria, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Gonzalez, Michael, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Grant, George, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Greenblat, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Haas, Michel, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Hardesty, Michael, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Harris, Susanne, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Highstein, Jene, circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)
    - Hurkmanns, R., circa 1975-2000 (Box 139)